[breeze blowing faintly]
Mrs. Price, you can't just show up
unannounced in the middle of a semester,
and remove your son from the school.
This is not acceptable.
Someone so bright and promising,
killing themselves
after the glamour has passed.
I've been feeling better
in the last couple weeks,
and I'd appreciate
you keeping some distance.
We allow ourselves contentment...
and the heart brings us ease
in its good time.
So G-goo came on his own,
wanting a refund of a prepaid
card he bought last year?
Mommy and Daddy will be right next to you and
there may be some organ music as the curtain opens.
The shiny new white and big house will be ready for us
faster than you can say "Jack Robinson"
But I told him I'd ask my boss,
and then I texted you, Detective.
- ALISTAIR: Okay.
- So much love to everybody.
ALISTAIR: Love to you all.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- There.
- Thank you.
- Samuel?
- Sam.
Sam, we're here
Here. OK!
Dad.
Dad
- Okay? You decided.
- Mm-hmm.
- of-of clowns and acrobats.
- And elephants.
-Uh, "projecting" means it sends them out.
-Happy things.